-=藍光電影網=-
blu-raydisc.tv
下載更多藍光高清電影-3D電影
請到-=藍光電影網=-
九一 九二...
Ninety-one,Ninety-two...
在那兒  哪兒? 如果被他們發現了...
It's down there.  Where? If they catch us...
這兒的酒有上百萬瓶
There's a million bottles of booze in there.
你覺得他們會知道少了一瓶麼?
You think they're gonna miss one?
天氣不錯 先生
Weather is with us,sir.
我們將在幾小時後到達港口
We arrive in port in a couple of hours.
幹得不錯
Very good.
謝謝誇獎 先生
You're welcome,sir.
夥計 這種味道我從沒聞到過 即使廁所的味道也比這好聞
Man,I never smelt anything like this. Not even when you're in the crapper.
你的大便什麼時候好聞過?
Oh,what,your shit smells like roses?
嘿 看
Hey,look.
我來幫你
I'll give you a hand.
記得你說運的是酒啊  文件上是這麼寫的
Thought you said it was booze.  That's what the papers said.
船長 船艙底層有情況 快看
Captain,we have a breach in lower level. Look.
哪個區?  101
Which section?  101.
操 你來掌舵
Fuck. Take the wheel.
是 先生  操
Yes,sir.  Fuck.
關門! 戴上防毒面具
Close the door! Get the masks.
天U+5450
Holy shit.
快處理掉
Take care of them.
早上好  請出示護照
Morning.  Passport,please.
浪很大?
Rough seas?
還可以 只是派對上海過頭了 你懂的吧
The sea was smooth. The party was a bit rough,if you know what I mean.
伊比沙島(位於地中海西部)  是的
Ibiza.  Yeah.
謝謝
Thanks.
小時候 父親常帶我去釣魚
When I was a kid,my father used to take me fishing.
但我一直不明白 他怎麼知道哪兒有魚
Never could figure out how he knew where the fish were.
他總是准確無誤
They were always exactly where he said they would be.
安全檢查
Security check.
我看起來像危險分子嗎?
Do I look like a security risk?
請下車 帶上你的證件去辦公室
Please step out of the car and bring your documents to the office.
證件就在這兒 警官
My documents are right here,sir.
但計算機在辦公室
The computer is in the office.
帶上她
Her too.
她在睡覺
She's sleeping.
還有她的證件  好的 沒問題
With her documents.  Okay,sure.
什麼鬼東西?
快 它要跑了
Come on. You're gonna lose it.
快了 警長 快釣上來了
Close,inspector,you're close.
是條大的 向左 向左
That's a big one. Go left,go left.
別讓它跑了
Don't let him get away.
快釣上來了
You're close.
向左 左邊! 向右!
Go left,go left! Go right!
肯定釣到了條白鯨 需要幫忙嗎?
Must be Moby Dick you hooked. Need some help?
不 謝謝 Frank
No,thank you,Frank.
我在這片兒釣魚的時候 你還沒出世呢
I have been fishing these waters since before you were born.
快了 警長 快釣上來了
You were close,inspector. You were close.
幸運的是 我們法國人皆具幽默感
Good thing that we French have such a highly developed sense of humor.
恕我直言 法國人認為傑瑞·劉易斯是個天才(美國著名喜劇表演泰斗、制作人、導演、主持人)
With all due respect,the French think Jerry Lewis is a genius.
傑瑞·劉易斯的確是個天才啊  迪安(喜劇演員)才是天才
Jerry Lewis is a genius.  Dean was the genius.
不 迪安只是拿著酒和香煙站在那傜NNo,Dean just stood there with a drink and a cigarette.
但關鍵是他可以讓所有人都捧腹大笑
My point exactly. Anyone can fall down and get a laugh.
有多少人可以拿著酒和香煙站在那 能做到這樣?
How many people can do it standing still with a drink and a cigarette?
喂?
喂 我是塔柯尼
好的
恐怕我們的悠閑日子得提前結束了
I am afraid our day of leisure is cut short.
Marseilles(馬賽)那邊出了點兒麻煩
There is a big mess in Marseilles.
一個瘋子駕著奧迪橫沖直撞
Some madman driving an Audi at impossible speeds.
別那樣看著我
Don't look at me.
長官讓我注意觀察第一反應
That is the first place the chief told me to look.
但我會告訴他 你有完美的不在場證據
But I will tell him you have the perfect alibi.
像往常一樣
As usual.
塔柯尼
Tarconi!
幫幫忙!  對不起 Frank
Please!  I am sorry,Frank.
這可是第一次上鉤!  是啊 沒錯
It's our first bite!  Yeah,yeah.
拜托  好啊
Please.  Yeah.
停船 拜托
Stop the boat. Come on.
不 不行 弗蘭克  別這樣 拜托
No. No,Frank.  Come on,please.
詹森先生 您此行的目的?
Purpose of your visit,Mr. Johnson?
生意
Business.
什麼生意?
What kind of business?
環境保護
Environmental protection.
謝謝
Thank you.
部長先生 明天歐盟會議的開幕致詞中 您將說到...
Mr. Minister,you're giving the opening address at an EU conference...
工業對敖德薩(蘇聯港市)環境的影響
on environmental impact of industry in Odessa tomorrow.
關鍵內容是什麼呢?  很簡單
What is top on your list of priorities?  It's a short list.
只有一項: 環境 以及如何保護它
There's only one item: The environment and how to protect it.
在這個經濟全球化的時代...
In the face of increasing pressure...
工業競爭取得成功的壓力越來越大...
for industries to compete successfully in a global economy...
不可否認 目標有時會和殘酷的現實相沖突...
that goal can sometimes come up against some very harsh realities.
但是 更為殘酷的是一個汙染和不適於居住的地球
Well,not as harsh as a polluted and uninhabitable planet.
先生們 請原諒...
Gentlemen,if you'll excuse me now...
我得去拯救樹木 讓工業家們掃興了
I have trees to save and industrialists to disappoint.
您明天的演講稿  你覺得如何?
Your speech for tomorrow.  Any good?
將會令很多人生氣  非常好
It's going to piss off a lot of people.  Excellent.
喂?
Hello?
部長先生嗎?
Mr. Minister?
你是誰?
Who is this?
我是誰並不重要
My name is not important.
您插手的 關於...
I've been put in charge of the negotiations...
伊希歐公司在烏克蘭經營許可...
you are engaged in with Ecocorp...
是由我負責談判的
for issuance of their license to do business in the Ukraine.
不管你是誰 你肯定是弄錯了
You must be misinformed,Mr. Whatever-Your-Name-Is.
我已經永久性終止談判
I've terminated negotiations permanently.
如果您看過信封堶悸漱憟...
I think you will reconsider that position...
我認為您會重新考慮的
once you have a chance to study the documents in the envelope.
好好考慮下吧
I'll be in touch.
喂 這媯o生了事故
Yeah,there's been an accident.
地址是德拉薩佛雷斯路8號 請派救護車來
Send an ambulance,8 Route de la Falaise.
馬爾科姆
Malcolm.
馬爾科姆 馬爾科姆
Malcolm. Malcolm.
我是問你的要價 這是什麼?
I asked you for your price. What is this?
一個可能會對這個活兒感興趣的人
A man who might be interested in taking the job. This man will.
我老板說 你是最適合的人選
My boss said you're the man for the job.
你老板搞錯了
Your boss got his facts wrong.
關於我老板 你應當知道兩件事:
Two things you should know about my boss:
他從不出錯 他從不接受拒絕
He never gets his facts wrong,he never takes no for an answer.
凡事都有第一次
Well,there's a first time for everything.
但不是這一次
Well,not this time.
你不會想這樣做的
You don't wanna do this.
你沒資格告訴我該做什麼 不該做什麼
I don't think you're in a position to tell me what I do and don't wanna do.
給你10秒鍾改變主意
You have 10 seconds to change your mind.
給你5秒鍾 拿開你的手
I'll give you five seconds to remove your hand.
馬爾科姆 馬爾科姆
Malcolm. Malcolm.
聽得到我說話嗎?
You hear me?
馬爾 我是說過 你任何時候來 我都歡迎 但不是表示...
Mal,I said drop in anytime,but I didn't mean...
我無處可去了  放松點兒 好嗎?
Nowhere else to go.  Just take it easy,okay?
別弄我出來
Don't move me from the car.
只是想在救護車來之前 讓你舒服點  不需要救護車
It's just get you comfortable till the ambulance arrives.  No ambulance.
你需要去看醫生 你中槍了 我處理不了這個
You need a doctor,you've been shot. I can't take care of this.
不能離開車
Not far from car.
放松
Relax.
保持冷靜 你會沒事兒的
Just try to stay calm. We'll have you fixed up in no time.
他在堶 快 傷勢很嚴重
He's inside. Quick,it's serious.
這邊麼?
先生?
Sir?
移動他時你要小心  用不著你來教 好嗎?
You wanna be careful moving him.  We know our job,okay?
先生 能聽到我說話嗎?
Sir,can you hear me?
這輛車不...
This car No...
如果你能聽到 按一下我的手
If you hear me,press my hand.
這輛車...
The car...
慢點兒 小心
快到了
我在天堂嗎?
Am I in heaven?
事實上 你在地獄
Actually,you're in a bit of the shit.
你會幫助我走出地獄嗎?
You'll help me out of it?
這要看你陷得有多深了
That depends on how deep you're in.
不要相信任何人  絕對同意
Don't trust anyone.  Couldn't agree with you more.
來吧  不! 不能離開車!
Come on.  No! Don't leave the car!
這車有這麼特別麼?  跟車沒關系
What's so special about the car?  Not the car.
等等!
Wait!
我告訴過你
I told you.
不要相信任何人
Don't trust anyone.
我告訴過你
I told you.
我冒昧給你拿了套衣服來
I took the liberty of bringing your suit.
這是你工作時的穿著 沒錯吧?
It's what you wear when you're working,correct?
沒錯 但我不是在工作
Correct. But I'm not working.
看吧 老板? 我告訴過你了  拜托 Joseph
You see,boss? I told you.  Please,Joseph.
是你在表達我們意願時 沒有用對方法吧
Your approach was not very effective in presenting our proposal the first time.
謝謝
Thank you.
就像我說的...
As I was saying...
我們很有誠意去見你 而你卻說你做不到
we came to you in good faith. You said you were unavailable.
只給了我們一個電話號碼 我們與電話上的人簽了約
We contracted with the man whose number you gave us.
事實證明 他無法勝任
He proved to be ineffective.
現在我的生意還沒完成
And now I am left with unfinished business.
在我看來 這是你的責任
The way I see it,you're responsible.
我明白你的想法
I understand your point of view.
但我還是做不到
But I'm still unavailable.
老板 我能說一句麼?
Boss,can I say something?
還有誰想說話麼?
Anyone else wanna say something?
很好
Good.
給我找一個更聰明的
Find me a smarter one.
給你三秒鍾改變主意...
You have three seconds to change your mind...
否則你永遠也別想改了
or you're gonna be permanently unavailable.
一
One.
二
Two.
有個條件
One condition.
說吧
I'm listening.
我要開我自己的車
I drive my own car.
成交
Deal.
你的回答早就在意料之中了 所以我們冒昧把你的車也開來了
In anticipation of your answer,we took the liberty of bringing your car.
換了油 優化了發動機 拿出了所有不必要的零件
Changed the oil,gave it a tune-up,took out all the non-essential material.
更換了牌照 愛死它了
Left the switch-over license plates. Love that.
裝上了我們的全球定位系統
Replaced the GPS with one of our own.
安裝了既定程序的 這樣會更有效率
Preprogrammed. More efficient that way.
為什麼我要這麼堅持 用最適合的人來完成這項任務呢?
Why I was so insistent on using only the best man for this assignment?
我們在玩一個更大的遊戲
We're playing in a much larger game here.
不要以為這只是隨便的一份工作 把它當成任務來完成
Don't think of this as just another job. Think of it as a mission.
我很高興地發現 在對待工作上 我們有很多共同點
I'm so pleased to find we share the same approach to our work.
我答應了就會做到 你也一樣
I make a deal,that's the deal. Just like you.
你不喜歡問名字 我也是 我們都很謹慎
You don't like names. Neither do I. We're both precise.
報酬以外的事情 我們都沒有任何興趣...
Neither one of us has any interest in what we're paid to do...
那些是你的規則 沒錯吧?
beyond what we are paid to do. Those are your rules,right?
你忘了一點
You forgot one.
我一個人幹  我以為你可能會喜歡有個人作伴
I work alone.  I thought you might like the company.
我還以為你想要我完成任務
Thought you wanted me to complete a mission.
沒錯 的確想
You're right. I do.
等等
Wait.
什麼 你想改變規則?
What,you wanna change the rules?
每個規則皆有例外 今天就破例下吧
Every rule has an exception. Let's make one for today.
你說了算
You're the boss.
沒問題了吧?
Anything else?
那個手鐲 有什麼你該告訴我的麼?
The jewelry. Anything I should know?
你記得那些小醜通過了安全檢查 在飛機上卻能把液體制成炸彈...
You remember those jokers trying to blow up airliners...
想炸毀客機的事兒吧?
by sneaking liquids through and combining them onboard?
原理相同 只是這個更精制
Same principle,just refined.
離車25英尺...
Twenty-five feet from the car...
黃燈亮 那是第一管液體已經准備好的信號
yellow light comes on,signaling the first liquid is ready.
五十英尺 橙色
Fifty feet,orange.
第二管液體准備就緒
Second liquid flows into the chamber.
75英尺 你將會看到紅色
Seventy-five feet,you're gonna see red.
你們該走了
Time to go.
這部電話只設置了我的號碼
This phone is programmed to call only one number,mine.
過了向北的第一個收費站 打給我 沒問題吧?
When you pass the first toll on the road going north,call me,all right?
汽油和食物的錢
Money for gas and food.
還有問題嗎?
Any other questions?
系上安全帶好嗎?
Would you mind buckling your seat belt?
難道你不該告訴我 這一切究竟是怎麼回事兒麼?
Don't suppose you wanna tell me what this is all about?
好極了
Great.
海洋珍珠號請求貨物清關
Ocean Pearl requesting cargo clearance.
文件已送達環境署
The papers are with the environmental agency.
拋下錨 在碼頭等候
Drop anchor and wait to dock.
他們一簽署 我們就通知你們  好的
We'll inform you when they're signed.  Okay.
我知道你是怎麼回事兒
I know what happened to you.
但弗蘭克是怎麼回事兒呢?
But what happened to Frank?
情報局的梅德韋德上校已經收到所有的信息
Colonel Medved over at Intelligence has been given all the information.
他知道那是頭等大事
He knows it's top priority.
他想要您知道 他會派最得力的人負責
He wants you to know he has his best men on it.
他會避開官方渠道
He'll keep it out of official channels.
他建議您盡可能多的爭取時間
He suggests you buy as much time as you can.
警長
車能拖去實驗室嗎?
告訴他們開始吧 這兒完了我就過去
他說開工
操!
移開!
警察在辦公!
聽著 我不知道你在這事上扮演什麼角色 我也不關心
Look,I don't know what your part in all this is or isn't. And I don't really care.
你先加入 知道的比我多...
You were here first,you know more than I do...
把你所知道的 都告訴我
download me on what you know.
我一無所知
I know nothing.
你怎麼認識Malcolm的?
How did you know Malcolm?
我不認識
I didn't.
你差點就跟他一起死在車堣F 還不認識?
You just happened to end up in a car with a man you don't know?
我現在也跟一個不認識的男人坐在車傜NI'm now in a car with man I don't know.
你不是該打電話的嗎?
Aren't you supposed to make a call?
很高興接到你電話
Nice to hear from you.
客套話就省省吧 給我密碼
You can skip the pleasantries. Just give me the code.
一 一 二 六
1-1-2-6.
到了再打給我
Call me when you arrive.
布達佩斯那兒有什麼?
What's in Budapest?
匈牙利肉湯 啤酒
Goulash. Beer.
很好
All right.
我們重新來過 從正式介紹開始
Let's rewind here,start with the proper introductions.
你辦事兒不是從不問姓名的麼?
What happened to the rule of no names?
那條規則暫時放一邊
I'm suspending that rule for the moment.
我叫弗蘭克馬丁
I'm Frank Martin.
那你叫?
And your name is?
我叫什麼有關系麼?
What matters,my name?
我們現在同在一條船上
Well,we're in this situation together.
不是
No.
我們倆 帶著兩個都會爆炸的手鐲坐在這兒 目的地相同
We're sitting here with two exploding bracelets on,going to the same place.
這就叫同坐一條船
I'd call that being in the same situation.
錯 他們會殺了你的
It's not. They are going to kill you.
我知道
I'm aware of that.
十之八九 他們殺了我之後 你就是下一個
In all probability,after they kill me,you're next on the list.
現在 如果要阻止這一切發生 我需要一點幫助
Now,if I'm gonna keep that from happening,I'm gonna need a little help.
首先 我們有個問題
From the top. We have this problem.
你以為我不知道有問題麼?
You think I don't know it's a problem?
在你看來 我很蠢?
I look stupid to you?
我沒有說過你蠢
I didn't say you were stupid.
但是我們的確存在一個問題
But we have a problem
不過要解決的話 你也幫不上什麼忙
and you're not being very helpful in participating in the solution of it.
我不想再說下去了
I don't want to talk anymore.
好吧
Fine.
你剛說你叫什麼來著?
What did you say your name was?
弗蘭克 叫弗蘭克馬丁
Frank. Frank Martin.
弗蘭克馬丁
Frank Martin.
瓦倫蒂娜
Valentina.
很高興見到你
Pleased to meet you.
警長 GPS系統已經被拆掉了
警長?
沒錯 GPS系統已經被拿走了
伊希歐公司的人到了
The gentlemen from Ecocorp are here.
讓他們進來
Show them in.
你們好
Gentlemen.
部長先生
Mr. Minister.
很感謝您在匆忙
We'd like to thank you for reconsidering our proposal
重新考慮我們的建議  想不考慮都難
on such short notice.  You make it very hard not to.
嗯 對 我們從不接受拒絕
Well,yes. We do have a reputation of not taking no for an answer.
這些是合約
Here are the contracts.
都准備好了
All in order.
我們曾被告知 除非得到您的親筆簽字
We were told the ships couldn't be cleared
否則船隊不能清關
unless you personally signed off on them.
船隊?
Ships?
我以為只有一只
I thought there was only one.
噢 好的 是這樣的
Oh,well,here's the thing.
為了使這次冒險更具價值
In order to make the venture more profitable
我們需要增加份量 這樣才會更有意義
we need to process the material in a volume that makes sense.
所說的船 到底有多少只?
How many ships are we talking about?
加上在港口等待清關的 共八只
Plus the one in the port waiting on clearance,eight.
八只
Eight.
今年
This year.
保護環境並不能立竿見影
Protecting the environment is a long-term commitment.
你自己說的 沒錯吧?
You've said so yourself,haven't you?
我明天在敖德薩同樣會說
And I will do again tomorrow in Odessa
這些東西到了那兒再簽吧
where I will sign these.
我們真心希望今天就能解決這事兒
We were really hoping to settle this today.
我想再仔細看看 後面還有些附錄
I want to review them,now that there are some addendums.
對這種長期承諾來說
Twenty-four hours doesn't make a difference
多二十四小時有何不同呢?
on such a long-term commitment,will it?
好吧 當然不會
No,of course not.
那麼 明天敖德薩見 早上9點
Then I will see you tomorrow in Odessa. Let's say 9 a.m.
好的
Yes.
好的 我等著
Okay,I'll stay.
但是原料正在四處泄漏  然後呢?
But the material is leaking everywhere.  And?
我們隱瞞不下去了  我會處理的 再給我多點時間
We won't be able to hide it.  I'll take care of it,just give me some time.
要是他們查起來...
If ever they check...
別緊張 交易很快就會達成的
Easy. The deal will be closed very soon.
二十四小時 不能再拖了
Twenty-four hours. No more.
喂?  我為你們再爭取了24小時
Yes?  I've bought you another 24 hours.
到明天早上9點
You have until tomorrow,9 a.m.
時間綽綽有餘
That should be more than enough time.
有頭緒了嗎?
Do you have a lead?
不止是有頭緒
Better than a lead.
我們拿到了一台定位器
A location.
警長
國際刑警拿過來的片子
是通往Rohrdorff路上的一台測速器拍到的
聯系我們的德國朋友們
是 可是我要說什麼呢?
讓他們期待與我共進晚餐吧
我餓了
I'm hungry.
我們離啤酒和香腸還有100公婸愧NWe're 100 kilometers from beer and sausage.
我不喜歡香腸
I don't like sausage.
那你喜歡什麼?
What would you like?
小牛肉
Veal.
烤過的 和上胡蘿卜...
Roast,with carrots...
還有甜菜一起
and beets.
加些湯汁 配上馬德拉產的白葡萄酒
In gravy,with Madeira in stock.
不來個前菜?
Nothing to start?
一份沙拉
A salad.
用從摩地納運來的意大利黑醋
Greens tossed with balsamic.
拌的青菜
From Modena.
醃制的?
Aged?
當然 醃過的
Of course,aged.
那甜點呢?
And for dessert?
薩赫蛋糕
Sachertorte.
要抹生奶油嗎?
With whipped cream or without?
當然
With.
喝的呢?
To drink?
葡萄酒
Wine.
或許 托卡葡萄酒?
Tokaj,perhaps?
加冰麼
Ice wine.
當然
Of course.
方向錯誤
你在幹什麼?  去見一個對首飾很在行的人
What are you doing?   Seeing a man about some jewelry.
偏離路線
他走錯了道
He's gone off the reservation.
派人去教教他該怎麼走
Send someone to get him back on.
別殺他
Don't kill him.
弗蘭克 見到你太好了 朋友
Frank. It's so good to see you,mein Freund.
我也很高興見到你 奧托
Good to see you too,Otto.
怎麼沒跟我說還帶了女朋友來的啊
You didn't mention you bring company.
不是女朋友
It's not really company.
那個...
It's...
有點複雜
complicated.
跟著你 有什麼會不複雜的
With you,it's always complicated. But you can tell me about it...
我准備了一份美味的炸豬排和土豆色拉 我們可以邊吃邊談...
over a nice schnitzel with Kartoffelsalat I have prepared.
嘿 奧托 你知道我愛吃你做的炸豬排
Hey,Otto,you know I love your schnitzel
但是我們首先得擺脫這個
but we need to get rid of this first.
二元自由形式磁性分解技術
Binary free-form magnetic-resolution technology.
說英語 拜托 Otto
English,please,Otto.
五角大樓通過他們的一家附屬公司
There's a program the Pentagon has funded
出資贊助了一個
through one of their subsidiary front companies
基於磁引力理論的
that's been experimenting with this new kind of weaponry
研發新型武器的項目
based on the theory of magnetic attraction.
這是極度機密的事情
Very hush-hush stuff.
我可不知道你在五角大樓的極度機密的消息圈內
I didn't realize you were in the loop on the Pentagon hush-hush.
當你任由你的手指在互聯網上漫步時
You wouldn't believe what you can discover
你所發現的東西 會讓你覺得難以置信
when you left your fingers walking through the Internet.
你想看看入侵伊朗的計劃書嗎?
You wanna see the invasion plans for Iran?
下次吧
Maybe some other time.
現在 我們得把這玩意兒弄下來 不然被轟到伊朗去的就是我了
Right now we need to get this thing off without blowing myself to Iran.
我不想拿細節來煩你
I don't wanna bother you with the details
但是 通常都會有個發射器在附近的
but usually there's a transmitter plate close by.
你不必這樣做
You should not be doing this.
之前你不想說 現在你又來勸告
First you don't talk,now you offer advice.
不是勸告 是警告
Not advice. A warning.
噢 你不認為警告來得有點遲了嗎?
Well,a little late for warnings,don't you think?
我同意你
I agree with you.
你偏離路線了
You're off course.
我繼續嗎?  沒錯 繼續
Should I?   Yeah,you should.
聽著 夥計們
Look,fellas
車子有點小問題 需要檢查一下
some things in the car were a bit off,needed checking.
男人就得跟他駕駛的車一樣棒 這是職業經驗
In my profession,a man is only as good as the car he drives.
你照顧好車 車就會照顧好你
You take care of the car,the car will take care of you.
老板說 "回到路上"
The boss says," Back on the road."
弗蘭克?
Frank?
你繼續
Keep at it.
回車堨h Frank
Back in the car,Frank.
不
No.
找到了?  還沒
Find it?   Not yet.
你是機靈的家夥?
You're the smart one?
不 我是大家夥
No. I'm the big one.
你不再是大家夥了 是吧?
Not so big anymore,are you?
找到了
Found it.
發射器  能拆下來麼?
The transmitter.  Can you remove it?
有線連著
It's wired.
要是我拆了: 就爆了
If I do: it comes boom.
打得很漂亮
You fight good.
但領帶打很爛
But your tie bad.
去哪兒?
Where are you going?
累了
Tired.
那就是我更願意與車相處的原因
That's why I prefer to deal with cars.
英雄所見略同
That makes two of us.
他們醒過來之後...? 醒了之後 我要怎麼辦?
What do you want me to do when they? When they wake up?
或許今天先放個假
Probably best to take the rest of the day off.
我很不爽
I'm not amused.
要是你不死 你會更不爽
You'd be less amused if you ended up dead.
如果你想我死 我早就死了 你想讓我活著
If you wanted me dead,I'd be dead. You need me alive.
你想要我完成這個任務 我要說明一下
You want me to complete the job,I need some clarification.
我在聽
I'm listening.
單獨聽
In person.
是單獨聽的
We've already done in person.
噢 顯然我不滿意
Well,not to my satisfaction,apparently.
現在 我是否滿意是你首要關心的問題
Right now,my satisfaction should be your main concern.
同一地點 一小時後 等我電話
Same place. One hour. Wait for my call.
喂?
Hello?
你讓我很失望
You've disappointed me.
你不是第一個 也不會是最後一個
You won't be the first and you won't be the last.
我告訴過你 我想一個人做這事兒  那沒必要 你看...
I told you I wanted to do this in person.  That won't be necessary. You see...
在我們一開始的少許交談後
since our little chat at the beginning
我就一直在想 其實我不需要找最優秀的人來做這種任務
I've been thinking I don't need the best for this mundane assignment.
任何持有駕照的白癡都能做到
Any idiot with a driver's license will do.
所以 引用偉大的美國人唐納德·川普的話:
So in the words of the great American,Donald Trump:
很抱歉 你被解雇了
I'm sorry,but you're fired.
你是誰?
Who are you?
你的新司機  我要舊的那個
Your new chauffeur.   I want the old one back.
他就快被炸成肉醬了
He's about to go to pieces.
你被解雇了
You're fired.
睡得怎麼樣?
How was your nap?
很安穩 你電話打得怎麼了?
Restful. How was your phone call?
簡短 系好你的安全帶
Brief. Fasten your seat belt.
塔柯尼
Tarconi.
是我
It's me.
我還在想你會什麼時候打來呢
I was wondering when you would call.
我忙死了
I've been busy.
我來猜猜 在布達佩斯?
Let me guess. In Budapest?
你也很忙嘛
You've been busy too.
用那種方式維系像你這樣的朋友關系 不會有問題 弗蘭克
Never a problem keeping that way with a friend like you,Frank.
那好 我就不多說了 告訴我你所知道的
So I don't have to be redundant,tell me what you know.
布達佩斯有一輛黑色的梅賽德斯
There is a black Mercedes also in Budapest.
或許並不歸你的朋友所有
Probably not occupied by friends of yours.
我只知道那個 現在告訴我你知道的吧
That is what I know. Now tell me what you know.
我有兩個包在後備箱 一個女孩在前座
I have two bags in the back and a girl in the front.
俄國人 我猜
Russian,I think.
我不知道她跟這一切有什麼關系
I don't know what she has to do with anything.
你試過問她嗎?
Have you tried asking her?
為什麼我沒有想到呢?  抱歉
Now,why didn't I think of that?  Sorry.
你當然問過了 那她說什麼?
Of course you've asked. And she says?
我快死了
I'm going to die.
典型的 俄國人
Typical. Russians.
他們太抑鬱了
They are so dark.
我還記得 在學校時 讀著陀思托耶夫斯基 然後想
I remember,in school,reading Dostoyevsky and thinking
這些人什麼時候才會笑呢?
when do these people laugh?
滿滿整頁都寫著
One page after the other
你無法相信的淒酸痛苦 弗蘭克
misery and suffering like you wouldn't believe,Frank.
警長 我們能省掉這節文學課嗎? 我這兒正閃著呢
Inspector,can we save the literature lesson? I'm blinking here.
那是密碼嗎?
Is that code?
不是 是他們給我們戴的像手鐲一樣的東西
No,it's some bracelet they accessorized us with.
如果我們離車太遠 就會爆炸
Wired to explode if we get too far from the car.
他們?
They?
是些美國人
Some American.
具體點呢? 姓名? 號碼?
Can you be more specific? A name? A number?
一無所知
Nothing.
你怎麼總是不當回事 弗蘭克?
Why do you always make it so easy,Frank?
天性使然
It's my nature.
你在哪兒? 我去找你
Where are you? I will come there.
這個想法可不怎麼樣 我們被看得很緊
That's not a good idea. They have me on a short leash.
要是你不告訴我點東西 我可幫不上什麼忙
I can't be of much help if you do not give me something.
你身邊有電腦麼?
How close are you to a computer?
喂 弗蘭克?
Yes,Frank?
被扔在市場上 感覺很不好啊
That wasn't very nice,back there in the market.
破壞規矩的人是你 不是我
You were the one who broke the rules,not me.
我承認
Point well taken.
我們扯平了 我們重新來過怎麼樣?
That makes us even. What say we start with a clean slate?
那麼這是個握手言和的電話嘍?
So this call is about kiss-and-make-up,then?
差不多吧
More or less.
你有去掉我手鐲的東西...
You have what I need to get the bracelet off...
而我有你要快遞的包裹
I have the packages you need delivered.
這是新坐標: 2-6-12
Here are the new coordinates,then: 2-6-12.
那會帶你到...
That'll take you to the place...
此次交易結束的地方
where we can have a conclusion to this business.
我等著你
I look forward to it.
弗蘭克
Frank.
追蹤到了嗎?
Did you get it?
查到了信號 再給我們點時間...
Got the signal. Give us a little time...
我們就能破譯這個數字還有位置
and we should have his number and location.
你的新手機 先生
Your new phone,sir.
還有別的事兒嗎?  沒了
Anything else?  No.
Frank 你這到這個坐標要帶你去哪嗎?
Frank,do you know where the signal is taking you?
我知道那兒有家餐廳 那兒的魚你從沒吃過
I know restaurant there. Fish like you never had.
跟胡蘿卜和黑胡椒一起烘烤
Roasted with small carrots and black pepper.
羅馬尼亞葡萄酒 倒並不怎麼樣
Romanian wine,not so good.
可是作為最後的晚餐 也不算太差
But for the last meal,could be worse.
你真該樂觀一點兒
You really should begin to think more positive.
我是個現實主義者
I'm realist.
我朋友說你悲觀絕望 還真是說對了
My friend was right when he said you were doom and gloom.
"悲觀絕望"什麼意思?
What means "doom and gloom"?
你知道的 你只會看到恐懼和害怕
You know,you only see the horrible and the terrible.
你的朋友 他憑什麼這麼說? 他又不認識我
Your friend,where does he get this? He doesn't know me.
他只是大體上描述了一下 一個俄羅斯人
He was talking about you in general. Russians,as a people.
我不是俄羅斯人 我是烏克蘭人
I'm not Russian. I'm Ukrainian.
抱歉
Excuse me.
不接受 我們是不同的人 我們這兒...
Not excused. We're different people. We're different here...
還有這兒 都不一樣
and here.
我個人覺得 你內心堶惜]並不完全那麼悲觀
Me,personally,I think there's a little bit of an optimist in you.
這又從何說起? 你又不了解我
How you can make such a statement? You don't know me.
好啦 我看到你正在化妝打扮
Well,I see you're putting makeup on.
要是你這麼確信我們會死 還這麼麻煩幹嘛?
If you were so convinced we was gonna die,why bother?
好看跟死有什麼關系?
What does looking good have to do with dying?
咦
Hello.
什麼東西?
What's that?
伊比沙島的特產 你想來一顆嗎?
Souvenirs from Ibiza. Do you want one?
不 謝了 你也不能吃 我們得保持清醒
No,thank you. And neither do you. We need to stay sharp.
好吧
Okay.
你保持清醒
You stay sharp.
而我 你怎麼說來著? 保持樂觀?
I stay,how you say? Optimist?
給我 把那東西給我 把藥丸給我!
Give me that. Give me that thing. Give me the pill!
給我...
Give me that...
天
Jesus.
好極了
Great.
真是好極了  別這樣 弗蘭克馬丁 高興點兒吧
Just great.  Come on,Frank Martin,lighten up.
我該高興? 藥丸起效時怎麼辦?
I should? How about when those pills hit?
你會海得跟個他媽的聖誕樹似的
You're gonna be lighting up like a goddamn Christmas tree.
那也不錯啊
That would be nice.
無聊 無聊 無聊?
Boring. Boring. Boring?
噢 耶
Oh,yeah.
你該待在車傜NYou should stay in the car.
你想我在車塈縉?
You want me to pee in car?
好吧 去吧
Okay. Go on.
別忘了
You remember.
不
Don't.
噢 不會吧
Oh,no.
別喝了 行不行?  怎麼了? 我又不開車
Stop,all right?  Why? I don't drive.
我只是想開心點兒
I want to have fun.
我想要開心點 你應該試著高興點 而不是老這麼嚴肅
I want to be happy. You should try happy instead of so serious.
保持樂觀很重要 你說的 不是嗎?
It's important to stay positive,like you say,yeah?
跟我一起喝吧 弗蘭克 我不想喝
Drink with me,Frankie.  I don't want a drink.
現在是誰悲觀絕望?
Now who is all gloomy and doomy?
我沒說錯吧? 悲觀絕望?
I say it right? Gloomy doomy?
快上車
Come on,get in the car.
我自由了 像鳥一樣自由
I am free,like a bird.
那個女孩! 快! 開快點!
The girl! Come on! Faster!
我丟了我的朋友!  我會再給你買一瓶
I have lost my friend!  I'll buy you a new one.
知道為什麼有輛車 追在我們屁股後面嗎?
Have any idea why we have a car on our ass?
不知道 我不在乎
I don't know. I don't care.
不介意小點兒聲吧?  一開始你說我悲觀絕望...
You mind?  First you say I'm doom and gloom...
而現在你告訴我不要太高興? 別變來變去的
and now you tell me do not be happy? Make up your mind.
喂 弗蘭克?  我想我們達成了協議
Yes,Frank?  I thought we had an agreement.
的確
We do.
跟我身後的那輛車沒有任何關系
It had nothing to do with a car on my ass.
我跟那一點關系也沒有 是不是跟你有恩怨的人?
I don't have anything to do with that. Someone else has issues with you?
可能吧
Likely.
我想是有其他勢力在辦事
What I think is that there are other forces at work here.
讓我查一下 看看能不能找到什麼
Let me check into it,see what I can find out.
那我現在要怎麼做?
What do I do in the meantime?
開快點吧
Drive faster.
他媽的他在幹什麼?
What the hell is he doing?
那兒!
There!
他在那兒!
He's down there!
我餓啦
I'm hungry.
早該想到買塊三明治 而不是伏特加
Should have thought about a sandwich,not vodka.
那兒!
Look!
那會兒我不是餓 是渴
I wasn't hungry then,I was thirsty.
你為什麼要那樣針對我?
Why you are so mean to me?
我不是針對 我才沒這個心思  "沒心思"是什麼意思?
I'm not being mean. I'm preoccupied.  What means "preoccupied"?
這就是沒心思
That means preoccupied.
射輪胎! 快! 抓住他!
Shoot the tires! Come on! Get him!
趴下!  射他!
Get down!  Shoot him!
搞什麼飛機!
Bloody hell!
開快點!
Faster!
快停車!
Stop the car!
噢 掛了!
Oh,shit!
你在幹嘛?
What are you doing?
你太緊張了
You're so tense.
用不著你來說
You don't say.
我來給你放松放松 如何?
I make you relax,okay?
好吧  我很在行
Yeah.  I'm good at this.
消除緊張
Making tense go away.
你幹嘛呢?
What are you doing?
我想在死之前 再一次感受性愛
I want to feel sex one more time before I die.
難道你不想嗎?
Don't you?
那跟你還有死 有什麼關系?
What is it with you and dying?
我有什麼問題嗎?
There is something wrong with me?
難道我不夠性感?
Am I not sexy?
不是 你很性感
Yeah,you're sexy.
噢 你是同志
You're the gay.
不 我不是同志
Nope,I am not the gay.
我不介意的
I don't mind.
我不是 好不好?
I'm not,okay?
那還有什麼問題?
Then what's the problem?
你有沒有想到過 可能是我沒心情?
Did it ever occur to you that maybe I'm not in the mood?
我以為規則是 不能打開包裹  沒錯
I thought rule is don't open package.  It is.
如果破壞了規矩 還要它幹嘛?
Why you have rules if you break them?
我也一直這樣問我自己
I keep asking myself the same thing.
電話薄
Phone books.
你才是那個包裹  沒錯
You're the package.  Yes.
為什麼不早說
Could have said something.
有什麼區別麼?  有
Would it make a difference?  Yes.
你要幹嘛?
Now what are you doing?
你知道的 在停車場...
You know,back in garage...
你脫掉衣服的時候 真是讓人興奮
it was very turn-on to me when you take off your clothes.
我當時正竭力不讓那五個白癡抓住我們
I was trying to keep five cretins from caving my head in.
我可不覺得有什麼好興奮的
I don't see the turn-on in that.
你以為 只有男人才會被脫衣舞勾起欲望?
You think it's only man gets turned on by striptease?
我可不喜歡事情變成這樣 瓦倫蒂娜
I don't like where this is going,Valentina.
你能為我再脫一次嗎?
Would you striptease for me again?
給我鑰匙 這並不好玩
Give me the keys. This is not funny.
想要鑰匙?
You want keys?
別鬧了 這才是我想要的
I want you to stop playing around,is what I want.
也許這是你我最後一次好好玩的機會了
Maybe it's last chance to play around for you and for me.
這不是玩的地方 現在也不是玩的時候
This is not the time or the place for playing.
那為什麼我會在此時此刻 對你有感覺呢?
Why do I get feeling with you it's never time or place?
如果我需要分析 我會去找心理醫生
If I wanna get analyzed,I'll see a psychiatrist.
快 把鑰匙給我
Now,give me the keys.
來吧 弗蘭克馬丁
Come on,Frank Martin.
一起玩吧
Make playtime for me.
行了吧? 夠不夠?
All right? That enough?
不夠 那不叫脫衣舞 弗蘭克
Not enough. That is not a striptease,Frank.
脫衣舞得性感 你知道的 扭扭屁股
Striptease is sexy. You know,move your ass a little.
來吧 弗蘭克馬丁
Come on,Frank Martin.
你想要鑰匙?
You want keys?
我想要脫衣舞
I want strip.
讓我做這些 你知道會有什麼後果麼?
You know what I'm gonna do to you for making me do this?
打我?
Spank me?
只是開始
For starters.
把我綁起來?  你會喜歡的 不是嗎?
Tie me up?  You'd like that,wouldn't you?
我喜歡粗暴型的
I like the rough stuff.
真的嗎?
Really?
哦 但別太粗暴了
Oh,but not too rough.
交易是脫衣舞換鑰匙
Deal was a striptease for the keys.
新交易 吻我 我就給你鑰匙
New deal. Kiss me for the keys.
用點兒心
Like you mean it.
你有真心吻過一個人麼 弗蘭克?
Do you ever kiss like you mean it,Frank?
我想也許沒有
I'm thinking maybe not.
我猜 你是一個人住的
I'm thinking you live alone.
不論在家還是在外
Inside and outside.
我想 你並不懼怕死亡
Thinking it is not dying you're afraid of.
而是懼怕生活
It's living.
跟我一起生活吧
Live with me.
就這一次
Just this once.
就這會兒 跟我一起生活
Just this moment. Live with me.
他的位置在哪?  我們跟丟了
What's his position?  We lost him.
他進了山區 我們接收不到那堛澈H號
He headed into the mountains. We can't get reception up there.
侵入軍用衛星
Hack into one of the military satellites.
是我
Yes.
你覺得我們是在玩遊戲嗎 部長先生?
You think we're playing games here,Mr Minister?
我不知道你在說什麼
I don't know what you're talking about.
我在說一輛載著你無能手下的黑色轎車
I'm talking about a black car full of your incompetent operatives.
再有這樣的動作 你就再也別想見到你女兒
One more move like that and you will never see your daughter again.
我想聽聽她的聲音
I want to hear her voice.
等合約簽好傳過來之後吧
When the contract is signed and delivered.
聽不到她的聲音 我是不會簽的
I will not sign until I hear her voice.
你沒有強硬的資格 部長先生
You are in no position to play hardball,Mr Minister.
那好 你也沒有 Johnson先生
Well,neither are you,Mr Johnson.
沒錯 我知道你是誰
Yes,I know who you are.
我敢保證 如果我女兒有什麼閃失...
And I can assure you,if anything happens to my daughter...
我會動用我所有的權力
I will use all the power I have.
抓住你 讓你用最可怕的方式來償還
I will hunt you down and make you pay in a most hideous way for this.
開始行動
We have to move now.
接啊 弗蘭克 快接
Pick up,Frank. Pick up.
我正在伊比沙島 度假
I'm in Ibiza. Making holiday.
有人遞給我一杯香檳
Someone hands me glass of champagne.
我喝了
I drink.
然後覺得有點兒不舒服
Then I don't feel so good.
我去了洗手間 之後的事兒我就不知道了 等我醒來時 就在這車上了
I go to bathroom,and next thing,I'm awake in the car.
我問他 "這是哪兒?" 他說他只是個送貨的
I ask him,"Where is this?" He tells me he's just a transporter.
他的車開得很棒
He's pretty good driver.
當然 沒有你棒
Not like you good.
我告訴他 "求你了 我父親是個有權有勢的人
I tell him,"Please. My father a really powerful man.
很有影響力 認識很多人 讓我給他打個電話吧"
Big influence. Knows a lot of people. Let me call him."
他很害怕 他以前從沒這樣做過
He's afraid. He's never done this before.
本來應該很簡單的 載人 離開 來錢很容易
It's supposed to be simple. Pick up,drop off. Easy money.
有人告訴他 不能打電話 不能離開車
He's been told no calls,never leave car.
但我說服了他
But I convince him.
我打了電話
I call.
但我還沒來得及跟父親說上話...
But before I say to my father where we are...
上車 快!
Inside the car. Come on!
我們逃走了 但...
We get away,but...
有人朝我們開槍 為什麼?
There's people shooting at us. Why?
他們為什麼要殺我們呢?
Why they shooting at us?
他說他們開槍 是因為我們沒有遵造計劃
He says they shoot because we didn't go according to plan.
我說 "好吧 那是舊計劃 新的計劃呢?"
I said,"Okay,that's the old plan. What's new plan?"
他說他有一個朋友
He says he has a friend.
之後我就遇到了你
And then I met you.
見到你 我就覺得安全了
And then I feel it's gonna be okay.
你甚至都不認識我
You didn't even know me.
我當然不認識你
Of course I don't know you.
我說的是感覺 不是認不認識
I talk about feelings,not knowing.
如果你有那種感覺 你表達的方式真是有趣
Well,if you was feeling that way,you sure had a funny way of showing it.
對女人來說 有一點神秘感會更好
Better for a woman to have a little mystery to her.
不是嗎?
No?
不是
No.
是的 只是一點點
Yes. Just a little.
他回到雷達監控上了 先生
He's back on the radar,sir.
喂  你他媽到底在哪?
Yeah.  Where the hell are you?
在去布加勒斯特的路上
On the way to Bucharest.
地點換了
Not any longer.
新坐標: 3-7-13
New coordinates: 3-7-13.
打擾一下 部長先生
Excuse me,Mr. Minister.
抱歉 請稍等
Sorry,just a minute.
我是警長Tarconi 來自馬賽
Inspector Tarconi,from Marseilles.
說馬賽也不是很准確...
Well,not exactly Marseilles...
是馬賽東邊的一個小鎮 你想做什麼呢 警長?
but a small town to the east What do you want,inspector?
和您談談  我沒時間
A word with you.  I have no time.
跟您的女兒有關
It's about your daughter.
敖德薩 弗蘭克 我的故鄉
Odessa,Frank. My country.
你帶我回家了 謝謝你
You take me home. Thank you.
怎麼不去布加勒斯特了?
What happened to Bucharest?
計劃有變  變得好 我更喜歡敖德薩
Change of plans.  It's a good change. I prefer Odessa.
是嘛
Yeah.
我倒是期待著魚和胡蘿卜呢
I was looking forward to that fish with the carrots myself.
哦 這兒的食物更美味
Oh,it's much better here.
你知道基輔雞嗎?  當然
You know chicken Kiev?  I do.
我知道這兒的一家餐廳
I know restaurant here.
是世界上最棒的
Best in the world.
雞肉鮮美 還有黃油 當它溢出來時...
The chicken's so fresh. And the butter,when it's coming out...
你肯定不敢相信 會有多美味
Like you cannot believe,it's so nice.
你知道我現在是什麼感覺嗎?
You know what I feel like now?
餓了?
Hungry.
感覺安全
Safe.
這會像電影的結局那樣嗎 從此過著幸福快樂的生活?
It's going to end up like the movies,this happily ever after?
今晚 這一切都將成為褪色的回憶
By tonight,this is all gonna be a fading memory.
你跟我微笑著坐在基輔雞店傜NIt's gonna be you and me,laughing over chicken Kiev.
騙子
Liar.
部長先生 決定做好了吧
Mr. Minister,an update,please.
我准備好了 一旦跟我女兒通過話 就可以簽合同
I am ready to sign the contract once I speak to my daughter.
喂? 喂?
Hello? Hello?
把筆准備好 一會兒打給你
Have that pen ready. I'll call you back.
喂  我們要收網了 弗蘭克
Yeah.  We are closing the noose,Frank.
好吧 收網的時候 確保沒人來把我拖下車
Well,when it closes,make sure no one tries to drag me out of the car.
你現在知道這是怎麼回事了嗎?
You know what this is about yet?
那個女孩 她父親
The girl. Her father.
和大量的有毒廢料
Large amounts of toxic waste.
這是一場交易 他的簽名換她的命
It is a trade. His signature for her life.
我有我的信譽 警長
I have a reputation to uphold here,inspector.
完成送貨任務率是百分之百
One hundred percent successful delivery rate.
我好像聽出來點兒什麼苗頭?
Am I detecting a little attachment?
那不是我所認識的弗蘭克 他的規則是 不問姓名 不牽涉感情
That is not the Frank I know. With his rules,no names,no attachment.
為什麼每個人都對我的規則那麼感興趣?
Why is everyone so concerned about my rules?
弗蘭克 我一直認為 其實你的內心是浪漫的
Frank,I always suspected you are a romantic at heart.
還有別的事兒嗎?
Anything else?
目的地在哪兒?
Where is the rendezvous?
我再打給你
I'll call you back.
喂  快結束了 弗蘭克
Yeah.  We're almost at the end,Frank.
把坐標給我  沒有坐標了
Just give me the coordinates.  No more coordinates.
就在你現在那條路上
The road you're on.
第一個路口左拐
Make your first left.
我想知道我要去哪兒
I'd like to know where I'm going.
到了你就知道了
You'll know when you get there.
不要擔心 這地方正是我想帶他們來的
Don't worry. We got them right where we want them.
我很欣賞你 弗蘭克
My compliments,Frank.
你的能力果然值得我們信任
Our trust in your abilities was well deserved.
現在你可以讓那女孩出來了
Now if you could please send the girl out.
她馬上出去
She's coming.
我不走
I'm not coming.
他們需要你 他們不會殺你的
They need you. They won't kill you.
但他們會殺你
But they will kill you.
難道我看上去像那種穿越半個歐洲 然後死在橋上的人嗎?
Do I look like a man who came halfway across Europe to die on a bridge?
我像嗎?
Do I?
我們可沒有這麼多耐心 弗蘭克
We don't have all day,Frank.
他們有那麼多人
Look how many of them.
他們都有槍
They have all the guns.
怎麼會沒事呢?
How it's gonna be okay?
晚飯的時候告訴你
Tell you over dinner.
現在 走吧
Now,go.
走啊
Go.
吻我
Kiss me.
去吧
Go.
你會害死我的 快 出去
You're gonna get me killed. Now,go.
抓她啊 混蛋
Get to her,you bastard.
親愛的 好點了嗎?
Better now,darling?
幹掉他
Finish him.
不! 弗蘭克!
No! Frank!
他的愛車將成為他的墳墓
His beloved car will be his grave.
爬出來 他會被炸死 留堶 他會被淹死 我們撤吧
Leaves it,he blows. Stays,he drowns. Let's get out of here.
Tarconi  女孩在他們手上
Tarconi.  They have the girl.
弗蘭克 我們試著從手機信號追蹤他
Frank,we are trying to track him through the phone signal.
你在哪兒?  湖傜NWhere are you?  In a lake.
湖?
A lake?
你能具體點嗎?
Can you be more specific?
這有個水壩
There's a dam.
水壩?  我知道那個地方 長官
A dam?  I know the place,sir.
多遠?  至少要十分鍾
How far?  Ten minutes at least.
弗蘭克 我們十分鍾左右到
Frank,we'll be there in 10 minutes.
能快點兒嗎?
Can you make it any faster?
我們會盡力的  謝謝
We'll do our best.  Thank you.
把全部人的票都買了
Buy tickets for all of us.
去哪兒?
Where to?
不管這車去哪兒 我們得繼續走半個小時
Anywhere this train is going. We need to keep moving for half an hour.
為什麼我們不繼續開車走呢?
Why don't we just keep driving around?
改日再算
Another day.
長官! 那兒!
Sir! There!
出去 出去!   所有人都出去!
Out. Out!  Everybody out!
快  滾!
Come on.  Move!
出去 快點!
Move,quick!
部長先生?  是的
Mr. Minister?  Yes.
有人想跟你談談
Someone wants to talk to you.
爸爸  你還好嗎?
Papa.  Are you all right?
不要簽
Don't sign.
你還有15分鍾
What you have is 15 minutes.
你有沒有查出這究竟是怎麼回事?  廢料
You ever find out what this is about?  Garbage.
我們談的是多少廢料呢?
How much garbage are we talking?
足夠汙染半個國家一百年的廢料
Enough to pollute half the country for a hundred years.
再試一次
Try it again.
作為一個現代女性 你是相當的無知
For a modern woman,you are very uninformed.
這是個新世界
This is the new world.
不再有國家 那是舊的觀念
There are no more countries. That's old think.
只有現實的經濟利益 贏利和虧損
There are just economic realities. Profit and loss.
效率和浪費
Efficiency and waste.
放眼全球 不再有地域之分
Think global,not local.
去你媽的
Think this.
喂?  進展如何?
Yes?  Where are we?
快完成了
We're almost there.
在哪?
Where?
這兒 他在火車上
Here. He is on a train.
我們在哪兒?  這兒
And where are we?  Here.
我們可以在那兒跟火車接上頭
We can get units there.
這個主意不錯 就這麼辦
That's a good idea. Do that.
哦 弗蘭克 拜托
Oh,Frank,come on.
部長先生 我向您保證 一切盡在掌握之中
Mr. Minister,I assure you,everything is in order.
我相信是的
I'm sure it is.
如果有什麼問題  我知道你們會解決的
If there are any problems I know you will solve them.
現在 請先出去吧...
Now,if you don't mind...
你可能不信 但在我內心 我是一個和平主義者
You might not believe this,but I am,at heart,a pacifist.
我討厭暴力
I hate violence.
暴力造成的問題比能解決的要多
It creates more problems than it solves.
現在的一切 也並不是我所願意的
You know,I never wanted to do any of this.
客戶提出了要求...
A client asked me to obtain a result...
但我想用最少的血...
so I went about creating an environment...
來達到他的要求
with the least amount of bloodshed.
可是沒有人願意合作 你不想 第一個司機不想...
No one wanted to cooperate. Not you,not the first driver...
你父親不想 剛死掉的弗蘭克馬丁也不想
not your father,not the recently deceased Frank Martin.
每個人都想反抗
Everyone wanted to fight.
有什麼好笑的?
What's so funny?
聽一個死人說話
Hearing a dead man talking.
再走走試試啊 弗蘭克
One more step,Frank.
來吧 再走走
Come on. One more.
看
Look.
已經結束了
It's over.
8:58 他簽了
Two minutes to 9. He signed.
哦 天U+5450
Oh,my God.
不要 弗蘭克 不 不要
No,Frank. No,no.
結束了 弗蘭克 結束了
It's over,Frank. It's over.
任務完成了 你和那女孩可以走了
Mission accomplished. You and the girl are free to go.
事實上 你的能力讓我印象深刻...
Matter of fact,I'm so impressed by your talent...
我可以給你提供一份職位
I'd like to offer you a position.
我也想給你提供一份 永遠殘廢
I'd like to offer you one. Permanently disabled.
我討厭浪費人材
I hate to waste talent.
但我真的不覺得我們合得來
But I really don't think we'd make a very good fit.
沒錯
That's right.
不要!
No!
我們是不合適 但你和手鐲炸彈是天生一對
We wouldn't fit,but you and the bracelet were made for each other.
不 不要
No,no.
不!
No!
不要!
你是在做正確的事
You're doing the right thing.
瓦倫蒂娜
Valentina.
我上天堂了嗎?
Am I in heaven?
看起來更像是地獄
Looks more like we're in hell.
我不在乎
I don't care.
只要我們在一起
As long as we're there together.
喂?
Yes?
部長先生 您女兒在我們這兒
Mr. Minister,your daughter is in good hands.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你在做什麼?  如你所說 做正確的事
What are you doing?  What you said,the right thing.
現在 先生們 失陪 我去要開會了...
And now,gentlemen. if you'll excuse me,I have a conference to address...
在會上我會說 跟你這樣的人做生意是很危險的
on the dangers of doing business with people like you.
非常感謝
Thank you very much.
逃生艇下水了嗎?
Is the launch ready?
在水上了 先生 等著呢  快逃吧
It's on the water,sir,waiting.  Time to leave.
帶上航海日志  好
Grab the log.  Okay.
我只是不明白
I just don't understand it.
小時候 我爸和我...
When I was a boy,my father and I...
總是能從這兒釣上來魚
used to pull fish out of this very spot all day long.
時代變了 警長
Times change,inspector.
人也一樣
As do people.
你是說我?
You referring to me?
我不認為這個言論很准確
I don't think that's a very accurate statement.
我開著原來的車 住在原來的房子傜NI drive the same car,live in the same house.
哦 我不是指你的車或是房子
Oh,I was not referring to your car or your house.
大海真是寧靜啊
The sea is so restful.
午餐准備好了嗎?
Is lunch ready yet?
小姐 事物發展是有先後的
Mademoiselle,there is a certain progression to things.
要吃午餐 得先釣到魚
In order to eat the lunch,you first have to catch the lunch.
如果我們繼續閑聊 還不集中精神的話...
And if we keep talking instead of concentrating...
我們什麼都釣不到
we're gonna catch nothing.
我有個更好的主意 為什麼我們不跳過抓魚這步...
I have better idea. Why we don't skip catching of lunch...
直接去吃午餐呢?
and go right to eating of lunch?
我知道離這不遠 有個很棒的地方...
I know wonderful place just up coast from here...
他們燜的魚 超級美味
where they make fish stew. Incredible.
用番茄和洋蔥 撒上少量的野生薰衣草
They use tomatoes and onions,and little amount of wild lavender.
配什麼酒呢?
What kind of wine?
桃紅的葡萄酒 南方貨
Pink. From south.
可能還是城堡媕x藏的哦
A Chateauneuf,perhaps.
要加冰  當然要加冰
Chilled.  Of course,chilled.
甜點呢?
And for dessert?